// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is not a source of light?",
    answer: "Moon",
    options: [
      "Sun",
      "Fire fly",
      "Moon",
      "Star"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of these funtion like our limb?",
    answer: "lever",
    options: [
      "lever",
      "pulley",
      "screw",
      "wedges"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Refraction of light occurs when rays of light?",
    answer: "move from a medium to another",
    options: [
      "fall on rough surface",
      "travel on a straight light ",
      "move from a medium to another",
      "strike a polished material"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Enviromental Hazard which does NOT result to erosion is?",
    answer: "pollution",
    options: [
      "burning",
      "flooding",
      "deforestation",
      "pollution"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The energy conversion in a boiling ring is ______ to _______",
    answer: "electrical, heat",
    options: [
      "light, heat",
      "electrical, heat",
      "chemical, light",
      "chemical, electrical"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The two magnetic poles which repel are",
    answer: "south, south",
    options: [
      "south, south",
      "north, south",
      "east, west",
      "west, west"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Dary products does NOT include",
    answer: "egg",
    options: [
      "cheese",
      "egg",
      "milk",
      "yoghurt"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is a third class lever?",
    answer: "sugar tong",
    options: [
      "nutcracker",
      "wheelbarrow",
      "sugar tong",
      "hammer"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "It is best important to properly dispose sewage to",
    answer: "prevent spread of disease",
    options: [
      "keep files away",
      "make our surrounding neat and tidy",
      "prevent unpleasent smell",
      "prevent spread of disease"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Ozone layer is found in the?",
    answer: "stratosphere",
    options: [
      "exosphere",
      "lonosphere",
      "stratosphere",
      "troposphere"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "A legal body which enforce forestry regulation is?",
    answer: "fepa",
    options: [
      "fepa",
      "nafcon",
      "nesrea",
      "fao"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which of the following food items helpsto replace worn out cells and tissues?",
    answer: "fish",
    options: [
      "fish",
      "butter",
      "rice",
      "maize"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "The main reason for annual planting of trees in Lagos State is to?",
    answer: "aid exchange of gases",
    options: [
      "provide shade for passers-by",
      "beautify home and office",
      "produce raw material for industries",
      "aid exchange of gases"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Fruits are nutritional to the body and should be taken _______ meal",
    answer: "after",
    options: [
      "after",
      "during",
      "within",
      "before"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Self esteem is ",
    answer: "feeling of self worth",
    options: [
      "feeling of self worth",
      "active listening",
      "open mindless",
      "feeling shy"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "If it takes 6N to lift a block with a pulley. What is the mechanical advantage of using the pulley if it takes 18N for you to lift the block",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "An offspring resembles his parents because he/she ______ them",
    answer: "inherits from",
    options: [
      "loves",
      "inherits from",
      "lives with",
      "wishes to resemble"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "The puberty changes occur at the ________ stg=age in life",
    answer: "adolescent",
    options: [
      "childhood",
      "adulthood",
      "widewood",
      "adolescent"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "The fraction of crude oil used in tarring roads is",
    answer: "bitumen",
    options: [
      "bitumen",
      "paraffin",
      "grease",
      "kerosene"
    ]
  },



  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "An object that is good conductor of heat and electricity is a ",
    answer: "metal",
    options: [
      "non-metal",
      "plastic",
      "metal",
      "glass"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "An advantage of personal cleanliness is?",
    answer: "emotional stability",
    options: [
      "social unacceptability",
      "emotional stability",
      "low self esteem",
      "poor health"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "A body that resolves  around another in space is called?",
    answer: "satellite",
    options: [
      "orbit",
      "axiz",
      "mast",
      "satellite"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "Maize >>>  Rabit  >>>   Snake >>>  Hawk.   In the arrangement above, the primary consumer is?",
    answer: "rabbit",
    options: [
      "rabbit",
      "hawk",
      "maize",
      "snake"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "The force that enables two surfaces to slide easiy over each other is _______ force",
    answer: "frictional",
    options: [
      "electrical",
      "gravitational",
      "magnetic",
      "frictional"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "Pulse taking is amed at determining proper functioning of the _______",
    answer: "heart",
    options: [
      "heart",
      "kidney",
      "lungs",
      "liver"
    ]
  },
];